To survive, they must obey.
Held is a horror, mystery, thriller film directed by Travis Cluff.
A couple's ailing marriage is put to the test when they are held hostage in an isolated vacation rental
by an unseen Voice that commands their every move and threatens harm if they don’t obey.
Emma, played by Jill Awbrey.
Henry, played by Bart Johnson.
The Voice / Nathan, played by Travis Cluff.
Ryan Sullivan, played by Zack Gold.
Joe, played by Rez Kempton.
Graham, played by Jener Dasilva.
Held is a 2020 American thriller film directed by Travis Cluff and Chris Lofing,
written by Jill Awbrey, and starring Jill Awbrey and Bart Johnson.
The film explores themes of infidelity, murder, masked
man, held captive, surveillance camera.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.